A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Civil War Commission, 1952-1966 (bulk 1958-1965)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Civil War Commission, 1952-1966 (bulk 1958-1965)
The Library of Virginia
26215, 27781, 28767, 31363, 36949, 38047, 40301, 40302, 53645
53.86 cu. ft. (157 boxes), 3 volumes, and 1 map drawer.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by James J. Geary, former Executive Director of the Virginia Civil War Commission, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 15 January 1965 (Accession 26215); 30 June 1972 (Accession 27781); 26 March 1975, 30 September 1975 (Accession 28767); 27 August 1981, 25 March 1982 (Accession 31363); 15 November 1999 (Accesson 36949); 23 March 2001 (Accession 38047); 24 January 2003 (Accessions 40301 and 40302); 13 May 2022 (Accession 53645).
Historical Information
The Virginia Civil War Centennial Commission was created on March 29, 1958 by an act passed by the General Assembly. The Commission was composed of seventeen members, with eight members appointed by the Speaker of the House of Delegates, four members appointed by the President of the Senate, and five members appointed by the Governor. Five of the commission members were named to form an executive committee. The Commission establised an advisory council of interested and knowledgeable people and employed an executive director to lead the Commission. James J. Geary, a former reporter for the Associated Press, was appointed as the executive director of the Virginia Civil War Commission and commenced working in November 1958.
The Civil War Commission was responsible for developing and coordinating along with state and local agencies, a "four-year anniversary" commemorating the centennial of the American Civil War. The Commission also promoted education concerning the Civil War in Virginia, as well as encouraged travel and tourism in the state. The Commission was granted broad powers, with proper consent, to lease or purchase property necessary for the commemoration, to enter into contracts, to adopt an official flag and seal, and to accept donations.
The Commission pursued two outreach programs, one focused on events of statewide signficance and another focused on community "grass roots" activities. The purpose of both programs was to honor Virginia's war heroes and encourage Civil War-related tourism. The first major event planned by the Commission were the opening day ceremonies which took place in Richmond on 23 April 1961, the anniversary of the day Robert E. Lee accepted command of Virginia's armed forces. Throughout its four year existence, the Commission worked with the State Highway Commission to develop a map of historical markers, sponsored statewide assemblies of local centennial committees, held a commemorative ceremony marking Virginia's involvement in the Peace Convention of 1861, assisted with the reenactment of the First Battle of Manassas (Bull Run), rededicated the statue of Lee at Gettysburg, and promoted the "Circle Tour" of Shenandoah Valley battle sites. The capstone event for the Commission was the observance of Lee's surrender at Appomattox Court House on 9 April 1965, an event that drew more than 10,000 spectators. A multitude of other activities and events not listed here were also sponsored, coordinated or supported by the Civil War Commission.
The Commission also devoted time and resources to creating and publishing a variety of books and booklets related to Virginia's involvement in the Civil War. The most well-known of these publications are Virginia, 1861-1865: Iron Gate to the Confederacy, A Guide to Military Operations in Virginia, 1861-1865, A Register of Military Events in Virginia, 1861-1865, Monuments to Memories: Virginia's Civil War Heritage in Bronze and Stone, and The Wartime Papers of Robert E. Lee. The Commission also produced several films about the Civil War, including Manassass to Appomattox, Another Cheer for Dixie, The Character of Lee, and Stonewall Jackson's Way.
A major achievement of the Commission was the construction of the Centennial Center, located on the Medical College of Virginia (MCV) campus in downtown Richmond. In 1960, the General Assembly approved a $1.3 million budget for construction of the Centennial Center and its exhibits. The building was designed by Walter Dorwin Teague to be very modern and much different from most of the architecture in Richmond. The center opened on 1 October 1961 and closed on 30 November 1965. After the centennial period ended, the center's exhibits were moved to the New Market Battlefield State Historical Park and ownership of the building reverted to MCV. The center was also referred to as the "Centennial Dome," and was later renamed the Jonah L. Larrick Student Center. MCV closed the building in late 2007 and it was demolished in May 2008. The Civil War Commission ceased to exist after 31 December 1965 and submitted its final report to the Governor in January 1966.
Scope and Content
Contains correspondence, subject files, maps, minutes, photographs, publications, scrapbooks, site plans, reference material, films, and audio recordings created and collected by the Virginia Civil War Commission. The material documents the creation of the Commission, its day-to-day administrative operations, and most importantly its efforts to commemorate Virginia's role in the Civil War. Topics include commemorations, state, local and national centennial committees, construction and use of the Centennial Center, exhibits, film production, and publications.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1952-1966
Series II. Scrapbooks, 1959-1965
Series III. Site Plans and Architectural Drawings, 1960
Series IV. The Wartime Papers of Robert E. Lee, 1959-1961 (photostats and card index, 1832-1870)
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1956-1966., Extent: 30.8 cu. ft. (Box 1-81d)
  Contains a variety of material documenting the administrative and operational activities of the Virginia Civil War Commission. This series comprises more than half of the collection. Included are incoming and outgoing correspondence, memorandums, financial records, reference material and publications both internal and external, newsletters, and photographs. The files document the Commission's publicity and advertising campaigns, the construction and operation of the Centennial Center in Richmond, Civil War exhibits, the various publications and films created and distributed by the Commission, and the activities of other state, local and national Civil War centennial committees. Of particular note are the files devoted to the Commission's compilation of Monuments to Memories: Virginia's Civil War Heritage in Bronze and Stone. Included in these files are photographs and histories of Civil War monuments located in Virginia. Restricted: Documents containing personnel information that are less than 75 years old. Some records may require review by an archivist and/or redaction (if it is possible) before they are served.
  Arranged alphabetically by heading, and then alphabetically by subject within. Arrangement within individual folders varies.
  - Administration.
    - Annual Reports and Supporting Documentation (1959-1961), 1959-1962. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report and Supporting Documentation (1962), 1962-1963. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report and Supporting Documentation (1963), 1962-1964. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report and Supporting Documentation (1964), 1964-1965. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report and Supporting Documentation (1965), 1965-1966. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Centennial Center Hostess Employment Correspondence and References, 1961-1964. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Centennial Center Hostess Reference Materials, 1959-1962. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Centennial Center Hostess Reference Materials, 1959-1962. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Centennial Center Hostess Training, 1961-1962. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Center Hostess Training, 1963-1965. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Civil War Background Material and Reference Files, 1961-1963. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Confederate States Centennial Conference: Correspondence, 1960. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Confederate States Centennial Conference: Correspondence, 1961. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Confederate States Centennial Conference: Correspondence, 1962. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Confederate States Centennial Conference: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1961. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Confederate States Centennial Conference: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1962; undated. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence of G.G. Lapsley (Hiring of Centennial Director), 1958. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Final Acknowledgements, Congratulatory Letters and Recipient Lists, 1965-1966. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Legislation and Resolutions, 1958-1963. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Memorandums, 1961. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Memorandums, 1962. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Memorandums, 1963. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Memorandums, 1964. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Memorandums, 1965. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Memorandums from Centennial Executive Director James J. Geary to Staff, 1960-1963. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Memorandums to Executive Committee and Commission, 1958-1959. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Memorandums to Executive Committee and Commission, 1960. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Memorandums to Executive Committee and Commission, 1961. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Memorandums to Executive Committee and Commission, 1962. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Memorandums to Executive Committee and Commission, 1962. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Minutes: Subcommittee on Centennial Center, 1959-1962. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Minutes: Virginia Civil War Commission, 1958-1965. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Memorandums, 1960-1964. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Memorandums, 1965-1966. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Information, 1958-1965; undated. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Information, 1958-1965; undated. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Information, 1958-1965; undated. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files (A-G), 1958-1965. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Files (H-M), 1959-1965. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Personnel Files (P-S), 1960-1964. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Personnel Files (T-Wa), 1958-1964. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Personnel Files (Wh-Z), 1960-1966. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Information (Centennial Center Closing and Employee Retention), 1964. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Programs and Invitations, 1961. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Programs and Invitations, 1962-1965; undated. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Records Management, 1961-1964. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Report of the Organization Committee to the Virginia Civil War Commission, 1958. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Report of the Preliminary Plans of the Virginia Civil War Commission to the General Assembly, 1959. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Reports to Commission Members, 1959-1961. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Resolution: The Purposes of the Civil War Centennial in Virginia, 1959. (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Seattle World's Fair, 1962. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Associations and Organizations.
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1960-1962. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1959-1962. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Central Richmond Association, 1961-1964. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Richmond: Correspondence, 1958-1965. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Richmond: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1959-1965. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Chambers of Commerce, 1958-1963. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Civil War Centennial Commission National Assemblies, 1958-1959. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Civil War Centennial Commission National Assemblies, 1960-1962. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Civil War Centennial Commission National Assemblies, 1963. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Civil War Centennial Commission National Assemblies, 1963. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Civil War Centennial Commission National Assemblies, 1964-1965. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Civil War Roundtables, 1958-1961. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Civil War Roundtables, 1962. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Civil War Roundtables, 1963. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Civil War Roundtables, 1964. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Civil War Roundtables, 1965. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Confederate High Command, 1958-1965. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Confederate States Centennial Conference, 1960-1963. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Confederate States Centennial Conference, 1964. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Confederate States Centennial Conference, 1965. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Ernest E. Best Business Services, 1962-1963. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Girl Scouts, 1960-1961. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - North-South Skirmish Association, 1959-1963. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - North-South Skirmish Association, 1964-1965. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Overseas Press Club: Correspondence, 1961. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Overseas Press Club: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1961. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Red Cross, 1961-1965. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Shenandoah Valley, Incorporated, 1959-1962. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Shenandoah Valley, Incorporated, 1963-1965. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Sons of Confederate Veterans, 1964-1965. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Sons of Union Veterans, 1964-1965. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Southern Heritage Foundation, 1961-1965. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1959-1961. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1962. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1963-1965. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy: Newspaper Clippings, 1960-1965. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - United States Navy, 1965. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - University Board, 1960. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - University Board, 1960-1964. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Association of Broadcasters, 1959-1961. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Hotel Association, 1961-1962. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Motel Association, 1962. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association, 1959-1960. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Retail Merchants Association, 1960. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Virginia State Bar Association, 1960-1961. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Battlefield Parks.
    - Appomattox, 1960-1965. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Chancellorsville, 1963. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Fredericksburg and Spotsylvania, 1960-1965. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - General Information Files, 1958-1964. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Manassas, 1959-1965. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - National Park Service, 1959-1961. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - National Park Service, 1962-1965. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - National Park Service: Public Use of the National Parks statistical reports, 1962-1965. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Petersburg City, 1960-1965. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Richmond and Drewry's Bluff (Fort Darling), 1960-1965. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Sayler's Creek, 1961-1963. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Sayler's Creek, undated. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Center Operations.
    - Acoustiguide, 1964-1965. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Attendance Policy, 1961-1962. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Attendance Summaries, 1961-1963. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Attendance Summaries, 1964-1965. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Birthday of Centennial Center Building, 1962. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Centennial Center Facts and Information, 1960-1962. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Center Opening Day, 1961. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Civil War Artifacts: Exhibit Loan Offers, 1961-1964. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Civil War Artifacts: Loaned Items, Incoming and Outgoing, 1959-1964. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Congratulatory and Appreciation Letters, 1965. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Directomat, 1964. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Exhibits: Design and Construction, 1961-1964. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Exhibits: Disposition of, 1952-1964. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Exhibits: Disposition of, 1965. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Exhibits: Disposition of, 1965. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Exhibits: Disposition of, 1965. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Exhibits: Disposition of, 1965. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Exhibits: Disposition of, 1965. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Exhibits: Kephart, Kip (Consultant on Exhibits), 1962. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Exhibits: Life Magazine Paintings Exhibit, 1963-1964. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (American Jew in the Civil War), 1962. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Civil War Centennial Year 1962), 1962-1963. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Civil War Prisoners), 1963. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Clara Barton: Angel of the Battlefield), 1962. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Gardner's Photographic Sketchbook of the War), 1961-1964. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (J.E.B. Stuart), 1964. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (J.E.B. Stuart), 1964. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Medal of Honor), 1961-1963. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (More to See in 1962: Recent Events in Interpreting the Civil War in Virginia), 1962. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Petersburg to Appomattox), 1964-1965. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Stonewall Jackson), 1963. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Virginia Attractions-Historic, Scenic, Recreational), 1962-1964. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Virginia Beckons), 1964-1965. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Exhibits: Temporary (Virginia Militia in the Civil War), 1962. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Folder and Brochure Orders, 1962-1965. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Folders, 1961-1963. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 1960-1962; undated. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1963. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 1963. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1964. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1965-1966. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Gifts to the Centennial Center, 1961-1964. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Groundbreaking, 1960. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Improvements to the Center, 1962. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Improvements to the Center, 1963. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Inventories, 1963-1965. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Invitations, 1961-1965. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Invitations to Virginia State Police, 1962. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Information Desk Reference Material, undated; circa 1955-1965. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Information Desk Reference Material, undated; circa 1955-1965. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Information Desk Reference Material, undated; circa 1955-1965. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Information Desk Reference Material, undated; circa 1955-1965. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Information Desk Reference Material, undated; circa 1955-1965. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Information Desk Reference Material, undated; circa 1955-1965. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Landscaping, 1961-1963. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - One Hundred Thousandth Visitor, 1962. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Permanance: Recommendations Regarding Future of Centennial Center, 1962-1964. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Richmond Activities Center Study, 1964. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Roadside Centennial Signs, 1960-1962. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Souvenirs, 1959-1962. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Student Groups, 1964. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Student Groups, 1965. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Student Groups, 1965. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Student Requests for Information, 1963-1965. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Teacher's Kit (1961), 1961-1964. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Teacher's Kit (1961), 1961-1964. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Teacher's Kit (1961), 1961-1964. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Teacher's Kit, Requests for, 1963. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Teacher's Kit, Requests for, 1964. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Teacher's Kit, Requests for, 1964. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Teacher's Kit, Requests for, 1964. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Teacher's Kit, Requests for, 1964. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Teacher's Kit, Requests for, 1965. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Teacher's Kit, Requests for, 1965. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Teacher's Kit, Requests for, 1965. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Tour Groups, 1961-1962. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Tour Groups, 1963-1965. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Commissions.
    - Alabama, 1959-1964. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Arizona, 1960-1961. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Arkansas, 1959-1962. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - California, 1959-1965. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut, 1960-1965. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Delaware, 1959-1961. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia, 1961-1964. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Florida, 1960-1965. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Georgia, 1959-1960. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Georgia, 1960. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Georgia, 1960-1961. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Georgia, 1961-1965. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Illinois, 1960-1963; undated. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Indiana, 1960-1965. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Iowa, 1960-1962; undated. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Kentucky, 1959-1964. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Louisiana, 1959-1965. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Maine, 1960-1965. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Maryland, 1960-1962. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Maryland, 1962-1964. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts, 1959-1964. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Michigan, 1959-1962. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Michigan, 1963-1965. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota, 1960-1963. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Mississippi, 1958-1961. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Mississippi, 1962-1965; undated. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Missouri, 1959-1960. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - New Hampshire, 1960-1965. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - New Jersey, 1960-1961. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - New Jersey, 1961. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey, 1962-1965. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - New York, 1961-1965. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina, 1958-1959. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - North Carolina, 1960-1961. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - North Carolina, 1962. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina, 1963-1966. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - North Carolina: Newsletters, 1960-1962. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - North Carolina: Newsletters, 1963-1965. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Ohio, 1960-1964. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Oklahoma, 1959-1961. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Oklahoma, 1962-1965. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania, 1960-1962. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania, 1963-1965. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Reports on Status, 1958-1959. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Rhode Island, 1960-1962. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - South Carolina, 1959-1960. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - South Carolina, 1961. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - South Carolina, 1962-1965; undated. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Tennessee, 1959. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Tennessee, 1960. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Tennessee, 1961. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Tennessee, 1962. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Tennessee, 1963. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee, 1964. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Tennessee, 1965. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Texas, 1959-1962. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Texas, 1963. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Texas, 1964-1965; undated. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - United States (National Commission), 1958. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - United States (National Commission), 1959. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - United States (National Commission), 1960. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - United States (National Commission), 1960. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - United States (National Commission), 1961. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - United States (National Commission), 1961. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - United States (National Commission), 1962. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - United States (National Commission), 1963. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - United States (National Commission), 1964-1965. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - United States (National Commission), undated. (Box 26, Folder 8)